Guide to the Harry H. Weintraub Collection of Gay-Related Photography and Historical Documentation, 1850s-2010.
Weintraub, Harry H. Collection of Gay-Related Photography and Historical Documentation
- Photographs
  - Posing
    - Small format, 376 photographs (Box A19)
      Includes COMM, ID, and 4x5 photographs by: AP-JE Productions (Hollywood), Arax (Paris), Art Bob, Art Studio (Denmark), Art-Kraft (WDC), Arts Unlimited, B&B Models/Photos/Studio (L.A.), BDR Studios (Buffalo), John Barrington (London), Jack Betz, Bog-Shop (Copenhagen), California Models/Al McDuffie (SF), Can Art/Frank Borck Enterprises (Toronto), Chris' Studios, CK Studio (Toronto), Culture Physique (Paris), Cummins/Discus (NYC), D&R, D.J. Ferrari/Ferrari Studio (Carmel, IN), Dan Studios (Beverly Hills), Bob Delmonteque/Mike Diks (Miami Beach and Hollywood), Denny Denfield (L.A.), Dom Studios (SF), DSI (Minneapolis), Eastern Model Associates/Don Young & Dick Lee (Brooklyn), Neil Edwards (Philadelphia), Europhoto (Belgium), F For Blond, Photo Ferrero/Jean Ferrero (Nice, France), Filmco, Dick Fontaine (Hollywood), Foto Grafo/Fotografo/Vulcanieus (Sweden), Gayle Photos, Roger Gibbons, Leon Graaff (Bressoux), A. Gray Photography, HRM Productions (SF), Bob Harvest (Paris), Steven Holden (Studio City), I.M.S. - Segelyset (Denmark), Kent Studios (Cleveland), JA Lang (Amsterdam), Tony Lanza (Montreal), Lingner (?) Photography, Lon of New York/Alonzo Hanagan, Lyric Studio (SF), Mark-One (Quebec), Dave Martin (SF), Michael Studio of Photography, J.V. Morullo, Rick Nielsen's "The Atlantis Studio", John Paignton (London), John Palatinus (NYC), Jeff Palmer, Quaintance, R.A. Enterprises (Hollywood), C. Rage (NYC), Pat Rocco, Troy Saxon (West Allis, WI), Scott (London), Rip Searby (Oakland), Spartan of Hollywood, Spectrum Films (Cincinnati), Starfire Studios (NYC), Studio Figurama, Sven Swede (Stockholm), Underwood Photographic Guild (Portsmouth, VA), Unity, Al Urban (NYC & Chicago), Vince (Manchester, UK), Visual Images Inc., Nick Vogue Photography (L.A.), Don Young (Brooklyn)
    - Small format, Photographs (Box A21)
      Includes packets, COMM, ID, 5x7, 5x8 photographs by: Anvil (L.A.), Arturo Studio (SF), Colt/Jim French (NYC), Rick Dion Studios (Portland, OR), Kensington Road (L.A.), Man's Image, Sierra Domino, Target (NYC)
    - Small format, Photographs (Box A24)
      Includes 4x5 COMM, UNID.
    - Small format, 116 photographs (Box A26)
      Includes sets, amateur, modern photographs
    - Small format, 246 photographs (Box A27)
    - Small format, 91 photographs (Box A36)
    - Small format, 160 photographs (Box A39)
      Includes amateur, vintage photographs
    - Small format, 350 photographs (Box A40)
      Includes contemporary, COMM, ID photographs by: Arimondi (SF), Gene Bagnato (NYC), Vince Barone (NYC), Vincent Cianni (Brooklyn), Allison Delarue (Princeton), William Doan (Fort Dodge, IA), John Eric (Phoenix), Larry Ferguson Studio (Omaha), Victor Giganti (Brooklyn), Michael Harwood (NYC), Mattias Herrmann (GER), Alan Joseph (PA), Joe Lalli (Brooklyn), Jake Onetarros (NYC), Adam Raphael (NYC/Ft. Lauderdale), Andrew Sellan (Brooklyn),George Spray (Arlington, TX), Bernard Spunberg (SF)
    - Small format, 350 photographs (Box A41)
      Includes COMM, ID, 5x7 photographs by: Alexander Studio (NYC), Arts Unlimited, BDR Studios (Buffalo), John Barrington (London), Jack Betz, Chris' Studios, Cummins/Discus/Anthony Guthyer (NYC), DSI (Minneapolis), David of Cleveland, Dom Studios (SF), Douglas of Detroit/Douglas Juleff, Eagle Studios (Chicago), Neil Edwards (Philadelphia), F For Blond, Filmco (LA), Dick Fontaine (Hollywood), Fotografo/Foto Grafo/Valcanieus (Sweden), Fox Ltd. (SF), Gayle Photos, HRM Productions (SF), Kent Studios (Cleveland), Lon of New York/Alonzo Hanagan, Lyric Studio (SF), Man's Image, Mark-One (Quebec), Dave Martin (SF), Metecue Associates (Ypsilanti), Milo of Los Angeles/Pat Milo), J.V. Morullo, Rick Nielson's "The Atlantis Studio" (NYC), Nova/William Higgins (NYC), John Palatinus (NYC), Jeff Palmer, Quaintance, Primus (Houston), R.A. Enterprises (Hollywood), C. Rage (SF), Mel Roberts (L.A.), Pat Rocco, Troy Saxon (West Allis, WI), Scott (London), Starfire Studios (NYC), Sven Swede (Stockholm), Al Urban (NYC & Chicago), Nick Vogue Photography (L.A.), Russ Warner (Oakland), Avery Willard/Bruce King (NYC), Your Model Service (NYC)
    - Small format, Photographs (Box A43)
      Includes COMM, ID, 4x5 photographs by: Bob Anthony (NYC), Artistic Visions by Greg, Bobby's Marines (SD), Castillo Studio (Ontario), Frank Collier (Erie, PA), Rod Crowther (WDC), Paul Dahlquist (Bothell, WA), Bob Delmonteque (Hollywood), Diva Photos (NYC), Peter Dvanadsas, Douglas of Detroit/Douglas Juleff, Embassy Studios (NYC), Europhoto (BEL), Photo Ferrero (Nice, France), Filmco (L.A.), Foto Grafo (SWD), Henri (Paris), Jackso Studio (Denmark), Janney (Philadelphia), J.A. Lang (Amsterdam), Ja Bee Studios, Tony Lanza (Montreal), Dave Martin (SF), Milo of Los Angeles/Pat Milo, Rick Neilsen, Paignton (London), Pete (Alexandria St., LA), Phoebus Verlag (Berlin), Mel Roberts (LA), Spectrum/Spectrum Films (Sinking Spring, OH), Studio 4 (Dallas), Titan (SF), Ulf-G-Son, Russ Warner (Oakland)
    - Small format, 60 photographs (Box A50)
      Includes packets/plastic binding strips, 4x5, 5x7, photographs of: "Polaroid", "Male Nude in Art", "Nine Male Nudists[on Film]"(Wyngate & Bevins, Holllywood)
    - Small format, Photographs (Box A54)
    - Small format, 167 photographs (Box A65)
      Includes sets, amateur, vintage
    - Small format, Photographs (Box A70)
      Includes 5x7 COMM, UNID.
    - Small format, 162 photographs (Box A75)
      Includes COMM, ID, 4x5, 5x7 photographs by: Alexander Studio (NYC), Kurt Deitrick, John Gamble, William Higgins, Latin Juice, Latino Fan Club/Joey Albano (NYC), Kent Masters, Sierra Domino (SF), Star European Models, Star Harlem Hardons, Star SHH, Third World, Victor of New York/Victor Mayo & Bill Vitale (NYC), Vulcan Studios/Anthony Guthyer (NYC)
    - Small format, 200 photographs (Box A88)
      Includes Polaroids, amateur, modern
    - Small format, Photographs (Box A70)
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B20)
      Includes COMM, ID photographs by: Johnny Adams (NYC), Mike Arlen (UK), Can Art/Frank Borck Enterprises (Ontario), Bob Chodale, Doug Codek, Kurt Deitrick, Michael Denning, Diffenbach, Pete Dobing Studios, Gems Entertainment, Graphic House (NYC), Gregg George, Jacque/Discus Studio, Kovert (Hollywood), Male Physique, Paul Matte, Charles T. O'Neal/Naakkve, Photo-Guide, Jorge Quiroz, C. Rage, Frank Ryan (Bronx), Studio Bes (NDS), E.J. Fisher Photo (L.A.)
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B24)
      Held by Donor, Includes COMM, UNID
    - Medium format, 105 photographs (Box B62)
      Includes COMM, ID, photographs by: Arax (FR), John Barrington (London), Bobco, Louis R. Charnicky, Climax Studios (London), Photo Ferrero/Jean Ferrero (Nice, France), Frank Collier (Erie, PA), Joe Corey (Cambridge, MA), David of California, Lon of New York/Alonzo Hanagan, Mark-One (Quebec), John Paignton (London), Paul Stone/Raynor, Sal Terra-Cina (NYC), Scott (London), Tony of Vulcan Studios/Anthony Guthyer (NYC), Joseph Weber (WDC), Don Young (Brooklyn)
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B70)
      Includes contemporary, modern photographs by: Amos Badertscher (Baltimore), Gene Bagnato (NYC), Salvatore Baiano (NYC), Ron Blunt (W.VA.), Bowman, Vincent Cianni (Brooklyn), George Daniell (NYC), William Doan (Fort Dodge, IA), Brian Eckerle, Victor Giganti (Brooklyn), Michael Harwood (NYC), Michael Henry (NYC), Alan Joseph (PA), Sergio Kardenas (L.A.), Joe Lalli (Brooklyn), Craig Morey (SF), Adam Raphael (NYC/Fort Lauderdale), Paul, Mpagi Sepuya (NYC), John Sonsini (L.A.), David Tucker (San Diego), Mike Walker, Lionel Wendt, Jeroen P.F. Willekens-Blighted (Netherlands), Terry Wilson (NJ), Robert Wolf
    - Medium format, 118 photographs (Box B81)
      Includes amateur, vintage, modern
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B101)
      Includes COMM, ID, photographs by: Paul J. Abrams, Champion/Walter Kundzicz (NYC), Galerie/Gallery Vitruvian (SF), R.A. Enterprises, Mel Roberts (L.A.), Russ Warner/E. Wallace Coombs/West Coast Models/California Physique Models League (Oakland), Avery Willard/Bruce King (NYC)
    - Medium format, 87 photographs (Box B102)
      Includes COMM, ID, photographs by: John Arndt (Seattle), Bob DelMonteque/Mike Diks (Miami Beach & Hollywood), Douglas of Detroit/Douglas Juleff, E.J. Fisher Photo (L.A.), Kris Studio/Chuck Renslow (Chicago), Quaintance, E. T. Schwarz, Al Urban (NYC & Chicago), Your Model Service (NYC)
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B104)
      Includes COMM, ID, photographs by: Colt/Jim French (NYC), Spartan (L.A.), Target, The Zeus Collection (L.A.)
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B105)
      Includes COMM, ID, photographs by: F For Blond, Emile Grecco (NYC), Latin Juice, Nova/William Higgins/Real Big One, Star SHH, Third World, Jim Wilkenson
    - Medium format, 69 photographs (Box B106)
      Includes COMM, ID, photographs by: Agence Theatricale Paul Calce (Montreal), Roland Akesson (Gothenburg), Bob Baker, D. Bowie, RA Cantu (NYC), Dennis Colby, A. Craig (NYC), Cub Studio, Neil Edwards (Philadelphia), Elysium, Inc., Roger Gibbons (L.A.), Graphic House, Hale Studio (Bronx), James Edwin Hills (SF), Jaybird, Kent Studios (Cleveland), Master Physique, Paul Matte, Craig Morey, Rick Nielsen's Studios/Atlantis (NYC), Old Reliable, John Palatinus (NYC), Photo Lanza[/Tony Lanza (Montreal)(?)], Real Big One, Savage Photography, Spectra (NYC), Jack Steele, Studio Bes (Amsterdam), Togof Studio/Melvin Sokolski (NYC), David Tomlinson (Hollywood), World Wide Fotos (N. Hollywood)
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B110)
      Includes UNID photographs of: Los Angeles collection
    - Medium format, Items (Box B120)
      Includes sets, COMM, ID, UNID photographs by: Dan Studios/Steve Kelly (Beverly Hills), Kurt Deeitrick, Roger Gibbons, Victor of NY/Victor Mayo & Bill Vitale
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B143)
      Includes COMM, ID photographs by: Paul L. Facchetti (Paris)
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B157)
      Includes COMM, ID photographs
    - Large format, Photographs (Box C2)
      Includes COMM, UNID
    - Large format, Photographs (Box C4)
      Includes COMM, ID photographs by: Gene Bagnato (NYC), Salvatore Baiano (NYC), Vincent Gigante (Brooklyn), Mark Lynch (Austin), Nigel Teare (NYC), Jack Slomovits (NYC)
    - Large format, Photographs (Box C5)
      Includes COMM, ID photographs by: Mel Avery (L.A.), Bruce of L.A./Bruce Bellas, Champion/Walter Kundzicz (NYC), Paul L. Facchetti (Paris), Milo of Los Angeles/Pat Milo, D.K. Parker (Phoenix), John Rusnak (NYC), George Spray (Arlington, TX), Russ Warner (Oakland), Western Photography Guild/Don Whitman (Denver)
    - Large format, Photographs (Box C14)
      Includes COMM, ID photographs by: John Barrington (London), RA Cantu (NYC), Champion/Walter Kundzicz (NYC), Douglas of Detroit/Douglas Juleff, Ken Haak (NYC), Alan Joseph (PA?), Karoll (Havana), M. Koch - O. Rieth, Lon of New York/Alonzo Hanagan, Dave Martin (SF), Lou Melan/Louis Melancon (NYC), Milo of Los Angeles/Pat Milo, Arundel Holmes Nichols (UK), D.R. Parker, Adam Raphael (NYC), Jane Shirek (L.A.), Michael Stratton (NYC), Sal Terra/Terra-Cina (NYC), Bernard Pierre Wolff (NYC)
  - Posing: Brochures
    - Medium format, 133 items (Box B84)
      Includes brochures by: All Star Enterprises, Bobby/Twenty-Nine Palms/Frat House Boys, Book-Nook (SF), Brentwood, California Casssette Co. (SF), David Carter (Venice, CA), Dan Studios (Beverly Hills), Jean-Paul David (London), De Zign (WDC), B. French (NYC), Griffin International (SF), Hangin' Tree Ranch (San Diego), Steven Holden (Studio City), Jocks Athletic Company, Johnny, Kamp Publishing Ltd. (Toronto), The LA Video Corporation, MMB (Santee, CA), MSR Videos, Magnum Studios (SF), Man’s Image (SF), Lee Mark (Beverly Hills), Dave Martin (SF), Maverick Studios (L.A.), The Odyssey Club, Palm Drive Video (Brentwood, CA), Palm Drive Video (SF), Photophysique.com, Pictorial Classics, R.A. Enterprises (Hollywood), Ramrods, Rho Delta Press (L.A.), Shotgun Video, P.R. Simon Productions (SF), Spectrum Films (Cincinnati), Glen Talbot Associates (Burbank), Tom of Finland Company (L.A.)
    - Medium format, 187 items (Box B115)
      Includes brochures by: Adonis Studios/Jerry Riskin (Oakland), Aaron Enterprises (L.A.), Adonis Studio/Jerry Riskin (Oakland), Amazing Productions (El Cerrito), Ananco Publishing Co., Art-Bob (L.A.), B&B (L.A.), Bruce of LA/Bruce Bellas, Book-Nook, California Models (SF), Champion/Walter Kundzicz (NYC), Brad Chapman, Classic Style (WDC), Coast (Beverly Hills), Colart (UK), Frank Collier (Erie, PA), Colt/Jim French (NYC), Continental Artists (WDC), E. Wallace Coombs/Russ Warner (Oakland), Joe Corey (Cambridge, MA), Cosco (Beverly Hills), David of Cleveland, Dyna-Men (Dallas), Donhar Printing & Publishing, "Golden" (Oakland), Golden Press, Hangin' Tree Ranch (SD), Steven Holden (Studio City, CA), Hombre/Tag/Tag Haggarty's Hombre (Hollywood), In Touch (Beverly Hills), Kamp, Rodney T. King (NYC), Kovert of Hollywood, Andrew Kozak (Hollywood), Will Lees (NYC), Lowry (Chicago), Lyle (L.A.), Lyndon Distributors Limited (Van Nuys), William M. MacLane Studios (Seattle), Magnum (SF), Malibu Models (L.A.), McDuffie (Sacramento), Mark III (Long Island City), Dave Martin (SF), Nova, Pacific Films (Albany, CA), Quaintance, R.A. Enterprises (Hollywood), Pat Rocco Films, Ramrods, Richard Roscoe (SF), Royale (London), Royale Photography (Hollywood), Sal/Soul Video (NYC), TYC Promotions (El Cerrito), Troy Saxon (Hollywood), Jack Slomovitz (NYC), The Sophisticate (Glassboro, NJ), Spectrum (Cincinnati), Jack Steele (Hollywood), Stephens Agency (Hollywood), TSC Studios, Thor (Chicago), Togof Studios/Melvin Sokolski (NYC),Vorton Studios (Chicago), Ken Wallace (L.A.), Warner Studios/Russ Warner (Oakland), Wessart (Portland, OR), West Coast Models/Russ Warner (Oakland), Western Photography Guild/Don Whitman (Denver), Don Young (Brooklyn)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B116)
      Includes brochures by: Kris/Charles Renslow (Chicago)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B117)
      Includes brochures by: AMG/Bob Mizer (L.A.)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B130)
      Includes brochures by: Colt/Jim French (NYC)/Buckshot Productions (Studio City)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B131)
      Includes brochures by: Ah Men (WEHO), Bob Anthony (NYC), Blueboy Enterprises/Young American Numbers (Miami), Books Unlimited (Hollywood), J. Brian (SF), BullsEye Productions, CAL (Santa Monica), Calafran Enterprises, Inc.(SF), Century Film Club, Coast (Beverly Hills), Colorama (WDC), Dimension (SF), DSI (Minneapolis), E.M.A. Studio/Ed McAndrews (L.A.), Filmco (L.A.), Fiurst Editions (Santee), Hartman Associates(L.A.), John Helwig (NYC), House of David (Hollywood), Jock (Johannesburg), Knights of Royale/Craig Stevens' Collection (Hollywood), Lugar Studio (NYC), Media Arts (NYC), Mustang (SF), National Productions (Glendale, CA), Quick Press International (Hollywood), The Photographer's Guild, Photografix (Culver City), Rampart, Pat Rocco Films/Male Film Festival/Park-Miller Theatre (NYC), S&D Products (L.A.), Sal/Soul Productions), Le Salon/Le Salon International (SF), Sovereign Advertising, Inc. (Philadelphia), Spectra (SF), Jim Stryker (NYC), The Studio Bookshop (NYC), Studio 9, TCS Studios, Telstar, Times Square Studio (NYC), Trade! Mark T.T.V.[Totally Tight Video]/Hollywood Video (Arleta CA), Trade! Mark Tyro/TYC (El Cerrito, CA), Vagabond Sales (Minneapolis), Viking Enterprises (Glendale, CA), Winchester Company (SF)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B151)
      Includes brochures by: Target (NYC)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B152)
      Includes brochures by: Falcon (SF)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B153)
      Includes brochures by: Old Reliable (Hollywood)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B154)
      Includes brochures by: Bobby/Twenty-Nine Palms/Frat House Boys [FHB] (San Diego)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B155)
      Includes brochures by: Nova/William Higgins (NYC)
  - Posing: Brochures/Gay-related Brochures/Contact Sheets/Ads
    - Large format, Items (Box C7)
      Includes items by: Athletic Model Guild (L.A.), Champion/Walter Kundzicz (NYC), Philmar (N Hollywood), R.A. Enterprises (Hollywood), Sunshine Beach Club (NYC), Treasure House European Models, Wyngate-Bevins (Hollywood)
  - Posing: Contact Sheets
    - Small format, 279 items (Box A71)
      Includes ID, UNID items by: B&B Models/Photos/Studios (L.A.), CK Studio (Toronto), Cal-Models (SF), F. Lee Collier (Erie, PA), Joe Corey (Cambridge, MA), Courtny (NYC), db associates (Berkeley, CA), Bob Del Monteque (Detroit), Douglas of Detroit/Douglas Juleff, Embassy Studios, Frontier Club/Frontier Athletic Club/George Greig (SD), Glennart Studio (Henderson, KY), John M. Hernic (NYC), Erick Holm (Stockholm), Hombre (L.A.), Hussar Photos (London), Ralph Kelly (L.A.), Kent Studios (Cleveland), Kozak (L.A.), Kris Studios (Chicago), Lon of New York/Alonzo Hanagan, Mark-One (Quebec), Al McDuffie (Sacramento), North Star (Toronto), John Palatinus (NYC), Quaintance Studios (Phoenix), Ritter Brothers (NYC), Royale (London), Scott (London), Jack Sidney (Brooklyn), Spartacus (Portland, OR), Stan (Gothenburg), Al Urban (NYC & Chicago), Vulcan, Russ Warner (Oakland), Young Guys Club (YGC)(Honolulu)
    - Medium format, 120 items (Box B58)
      Includes items by: Adonis Studios/Jerry Riskin (Oakland), Art-Bob (L.A.), Art-Kraft (WDC), B&B Models/Photos/Studio (L.A.), Ray Baker (Laguna Beach), Glen Bishop (Grand Haven, MI), California Models/Al McDuffie (SF), Champion/Walter Kundzicz (NYC), E. Wallace Coombs/Russ Warner, Rod Crowther (Chevy Chase), Bob Delmonteque Studios/Mike Diks (Miami Beach & Hollywood), Discus Studio, Pete Dobing Studios, Douglas of Detroit/Douglas Juleff, Greenwood/Cooper Homevideo, Ron Kramer, Lon of New York/Alonzo Hanagan, Lyle (L.A.), Dave Martin (SF), Photo-Guide, Richard Roscoe (SF), Royale (London), Rip Searby (Oakland), The Sophisticate (Glassboro, NJ), Togof Studio/Melvin Sokolski (NYC), Al Urban (NYC & Chicago), Vince of London/James E. Grabitz (Burlington, NJ), Ken Wallace (L.A.), Russ Warner (Oakland), West Coast Models/Russ Warner (Oakland), Avery Willard/Bruce King (NYC), Don Young (Brooklyn)
    - Medium format, 50 items (Box B127)
      Includes items by: Art-Kraft (WDC), Ray Baker, California Models, Champion, Col Art (Middlesex, UK), Delmanteque, John M. Hernic (NYC), Kovert of Hollywood/Jack Steele, Lon of NY, Lyle (L.A.), Richard Roscoe (SF), Royale (London), Warner Studios (Oakland), Talog, Togof Photos/Melvin Sokolski (NYC), Tyro/TYC (El Cerrito), Al Urban (NYC), Ken Wallace (L.A.), West Coast Models/Russ Warner (Oakland), Don Young
    - Medium format, Items (Box B133)
      Includes COMM, UNID items
    - Medium format, Items (Box B141)
      Includes COMM, UNID items by: AMG (L.A.), Mike Arlen, Continental Artists (WDC), E.M.A. Studio (L.A.), Frontier Athletic Club (Tijuana), Roger Gibbons (L.A.), Tyro/TYC (El Cerrito)
  - Postcards/Ads: Vintage & Modern
    - Large format, 130 Items (Box C9)
  - Posters/Athletes/Posing (Salvatore Baiano [NYC])/Portraits/Gay Life
    - Oversize format, Items (Box D6)
  - Prints/Drawings
    - Large format, Items (Box C9)
  - Prints/Drawings/Pastels/Water Colors/Roth [Sheboygan] & Wilson [Oswego] family houses
    - Large format, Items (Box C17)
  - Provincetown 1961, 1962, & 1963 Collection
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B165)
  - Publications: Calendars/Catalogues/Brochures
    - Medium format, Items (Box B122)
  - Publications: Physical Culture/Health/Bodybuilding/Ads/Calendars/Posters/Sheet Music
    - Large format, Items (Box C3)
  - Riordan, Michael (Boston)
    - Medium format, 68 photographs (Box B72)
      Included 4x5, 5x7, 8x10 photographs
  - S&M Original Fiction
    - Medium format, Items (Box B147)
      Includes: "Ferry Island", "My Name is Ralph Decker....", "Spread-Eagled on First Avenue", "That Second Trip to town", "A Thing of Beauty Is a Boy forever", "From the Golden Chronicle of Archiles [sic]", "On a Binge with a Dinge", "Dual Flogging on Balls", "Retribution", "Lord Nick & His Pals", "Dear Master ....", "Bum Voyage", "Aimez-Vous Shit or A Certain Smell", My Vacation to the South", "It's Only temporary", "A Couple of Days Off", "Begin and End as a Man", "His first Job", "I Was a Heterosexual for the State Department", "How would you like to be stranded at the age of 16....", "Initiation", "I Was a Teen Age Motherfucker", "Thus the anus was distended.... [starts on p. 21]", "Pick-Up", "Further Adventures of Jack & Dan", "Peeping Tom", "Marty", "He Knew What He Wanted", "Andante" "Peshawar Barracks", "Banged Up Butts", "The Window Cleaner", "Dear Rod....", "Initiation", "It turned out to be one of those warm days....", "Sailors on Watch", "Like Father Like Son"
    - Large format, Items (Box C18)
      Includes notebook with "Master Carlton", "Friday Night Poker", "Motel Madness", "The Motorcyclist"; notebook with "[untitled story]", "Leather Fun", "[untitled memoir ("I've just spent nine days as the complete slave ...."]", "Messenger Boy", "Saturday At the Office", "Story by John Age 16", "The Hideout/Initiation", "The Vacation"
  - Scouting
    - Small format, 67 photographs (Box A60)
    - Medium format, 26 photographs (Box B56)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Medium format, 3 items (Box B37)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B39)
    - Medium format, 4 items (Box B44)
  - Scrapbooks: Beefcake/"Snap Shots" (Harrisburg, PA)
    - Large format, Items (Box C20)
      Beefcake includes pictures inserted in old photo album
  - Scrapbook: Clarkson Memorial College 1920/Drag 1955
    - Oversize format, Items (Box D7)
  - Scrapbook: "Orlando De Benedictis Japan 1954-1955"
    - Large format, Items (Box C19)
  - Scrapbooks: Russian Army, "Write-Up" of Eric Lawson (Middle-weight champion of the South); "Snap Shots" of Enlisted Men's Social Center, Kodiak, Alaska 1946; Sketch Book with Tom of Finland drawings; "Boy Boy" parody by Greg Backstrom
    - Medium format, Items (Box B148)
  - Sexual Activity
    - Small format, 450 photographs (Box A16)
    - Small format, 265 photographs (Box A34)
    - Medium format, 129 photographs (Box B7)
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B8)
    - Medium format, 132 photographs (Box B31)
    - Medium format, 110 photographs (Box B163)
    - Large format, Photographs (Box C1)
  - Slomovits, Jack (NYC)
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B124)
      Includes 4x5, 5x7, 8x10
  - Spray, George (Arlington, TX)
    - Medium format, 144 photographs (Box B26)
  - T.A.I.L.
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B91)
  - Target
    - Small format, 91 photographs (Box A74)
  - "To Herm"
    - Small format (Box A95)
  - Tom of Finland: Drawings and Contact Sheets
    - Medium format, Items (Box B23)
  - Travers, Bruce/Cross-dresser
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B160)
  - Tressel, Mr. Collection
    - Medium format, 111 photographs (Box B89)
  - Vintage Greeting Cards/Invitations/Announcements/Olson, Frank Collection
    - Medium format, Items (Box B118)
      Includes calendars
    - Medium format, 150 items (Box B121)
  - West Virginia Collection
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B161)
  - Western Photography Guild/Don Whitman (Denver)
    - Small format, 281 items (Box A53)
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B64)
      Includes 5 & 2/8 x 6 & 7/8 sets in original envelopes, 8x10 photographs
    - Medium format, Photographs (Box B100)
      Includes 5 & 2/8 x 6 & 7/8 photographs
  - Written matter/Sheet Music
    - Large format, Items (Box C8)
  - Young, Dr.
    - Medium format, 7 items (Box B87)
    - Medium format, 88 items (Box B88)